

# Balázs Sárközi

Software engineer

#### CONTACT

Address

Phone Number

+36705973833

Website

sarkozibalazs.dev

**Email Address** 

hello@sarkozibalazs.dev

#### CERTIFICATIONS

# Sap certified ABAP developer

#### AWS solutions architect

## **DevOps Deployment Automation** with Terraform

#### LANGUAGES

Hungarian

**English** C1

German

#### TECHNICAL SKILLS

#### Web design

# **PHP**

## Node

Backend (express, adonis)

## Frontend frameworks

VueJs. React

#### System administration

## Infrastructure management

#### Circuit Board design

### Manufacturing

Fusion 360 cad, Grbl, Mach4

## **Robotics**

#### **PROFILE**

I'm a software engineer, with over 5 years of experience in full time professional freelance software development. I'm mostly specialized in web based solutions, with a focus on ecommerce, erp systems, and SaaS applications. Recently took up hardware development with a focus on robotics, and home automatization

#### EDUCATION

#### **Budapest University of Technology and Science**

Software engineer

(September 2004 - August 2011)

## University of Óbuda

Electrical engineer

(September 2018 - Present)

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## **Telenor Hungary**

(May 2007 - August 2009)

Key responsibilites: maintained old services and developed new funcionalities, mostly for the Telenor mobile portal, and other Telenor platforms.

#### Win Trade 2000 bt.

(October 2009 - June 2010)

Erp system developer

Key responsibilites: developing new features for the internal erp system

#### STV Services Gmbh

(May 2011 - March 2012)

System administrator

Key responsibilities: maintaining IT infrastructure, providing desktop support

#### Viale kft

(September 2012 - November 2013)

Full Stack Web developer

Key responsibilites: developing new ecommerce features

#### Aton technology ltd.

(February 2014 - December 2014)

Backend engineer

Key responsibilites: maintaining and developing existing backend codebase on an SaaS system.

### Freelancer

(July 2012 - Present)

Software engineer

I started working on side projects as a freelancer in 2012. Since 2015 its my main occupation.

## **PROJECT HIGHLIGHTS**

## Lisa Erp

#### https://projects.sarkozibalazs.dev/lisa-erp

Lisa Erp is a custom erp system. It handles the daily operations of a company employing 40+ people, including retail, ecommerce, inventory and warehouse management, finance, etc. Technologies: Php, Javascript

#### Abacus

## https://projects.sarkozibalazs.dev/abacus-procurment-support

Abacus is a dropship support tool, integrates 14 hungarian distributors, handling over 200.000 products real-time. The system is capable of tracking individual product stock status, price changes across every distributor and can manage connected retailer database. Abacus is managed through Terraform, can automatically deploy and scale. Technologies: Php, Laravel, Terraform

## Simpl@ eCommerce engine

https://github.com/garel/simple-shop

Simple shop is a simple ecommerce engine, built with Laravel and Jetstream. Jetstream is a new Laravel 8 frontend scaffolding, with optional stacks. The project uses the inertiajs stack with vue. The engine is a demo / experimental SPA

#### REFERENCES

IT expert +36302768727

## Becskereki Gábor

Arnold Velansits Developer

Tamás Wittinger Digital Platform Manager

+36704099257

+36306892713 kontroll@videojatekbolt.hu

Becskereki.Gabor@ksh.hu